(+521) 33 1320 2091

 \searrow

raul.elizalde.breton@gmail.com



ABOUT ME

I'm a technology enthusiast with over two years of experience in software development and data analysis who believes in working ethics and being a good co-worker. I take pride in my ability to deliver high-quality software solutions and have productive communication during the development process with my co-workers.



EXPERIENCE

(ask for more details if interested!)

Data Engineer Intern

JAN. 2022 -JUL. 2022

Data Engineer

JUL. 2022 -AUG. 2023

Jr. IBM

I B M

Full Stack

DeveloperUNIVERSITY OF
GUADALAJARA

FEB. 2023 -OCT. 2023

Raul Elizalde Breton

#3

EDUCATION

Computer
Sciences
UNIVERSITY OF
GUADALAJARA

Big Data Certificate

I B M

I B M

Data Science Certificate

UX Certificate GOOGLE JAN. 2019 -JUL. 2023

JUL. 2022 -AUG. 2023

JUL. 2022 -AUG. 2023

JUL. 2022 -AUG. 2023

DATA ENGINEER / WEB DEVELOPER

#4

SKILLS

(Technical - Soft)

• PYTHON

- PYSPARK
- DJANGO
- FLASK
- SQL
- BIG SQL
- AZURE
- GOOGLE CLOUD PLATFORM
- GIT/GIT-HUB
- HTMLCSS
- LINUX
- ETL PROCESSES

- ALGORITHMS
- DATA STRUCTURES
- ALGORITHMS
- DATA STRUCTURES
- POWERBI
- GOOD TEAM PLAYER
- FRIENDLY
- EASYGOING
- CRITICAL THINKING
- PROBLEM SOLVINGTIME MANAGEMENT
- TIME MANAGEMENTADAPTABLE
- PASSIONATE
- PASSIONATI

#5
LANGUAGES

English

INTERNATIONAL PROFFICIENCY

French

B1 DELF

https://github.com/raulbreton



in/raul-elizalde-breton-2172081a6

